https://www.saxoncourt.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content+886-2-2311-6000 [Ext. 129]applications@saxoncourt.comSaxoncourt Taiwan Ltd. Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from saxoncourt.com (the “Site”).Personal information we collectWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit https://www.allaboutcookies.org. – “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. – “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and the information you submit when you apply for a job.How we use your personal informationWe use the Information that we collect generally to fulfill any requests for services placed through the Site (including recruitment and job placement). Additionally, we use this Information to:Communicate with youScreen our applicants for potential risk or fraudWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or servicesWe use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).Some device information may also be used in remarketing to potential applicants.Sharing your personal informationWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Mailchimp (www.mailchimp.com) to distribute mailing lists and newsletters. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful requests for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.Behavioral advertisingAs described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.You can opt-out of targeted advertising by:FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymousAdditionally, you can opt-out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: https://optout.aboutads.info/.DO NOT TRACK Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTS You have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are an EU resident, note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of the EU, including to Canada and to the United States.DATA RETENTION When you sign up for a job or newsletter through the Site, we will maintain your Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.CHANGES We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT US For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at contact@saxoncourt.net or mail us:Boai Rd, No. 148, 4F, Taipei City, TPE, 100, TaiwanLast update: 2020 May 4applications@saxoncourt.com +886-2-2311-9858 (Taiwan)Privacy Policy Go to TopApply NowJob BoardSaxoncourt FacebookSaxoncourt TwitterSaxoncourt Linkedin
How We Help You Teach EnglishFrequently Asked QuestionsLiving in JapanLiving in ChinaLiving in ThailandLiving in TaiwanEnglish Teaching TipsEnglish Teaching Tips NewsletterLiving and Teaching Abroad BlogTEFL Discount
